Recognize multiple patterns example
Test the MI unit with the tester
Precise the number of patterns to find
Then it computes a range of threshold values
The 4 patterns are found in black
Each line is a match
between the pattern
in left and the scene
8 match is the minimum
to detect a pattern
You can see the threshold value (193) on top
Now we do the same for the power_supply
There is only one in the image
The power supply is isolated
with a threshold of 118
Now we can run the program
With the good values
Then we have
both the power supply
and the MI units
And here all the corners and names
To help you to find an appropriated threshold